# Wang Jin

Senior developer on mobile

#### **Email**

seniordev52@gmail.com

#### Address

China, Zhejiang, Hangzhou, Shangcheng District, 国货路35

### **Country**

China

### Skills

Android – java: 10.0

**Android – kotlin**: 8.0

Ios - swift: 10.0

Ios – objectiveC: 7.0

React-native: 10.0

Flutter: 9.0

Xamarin: 10.0

**Ionic-angular**: 9.0

Laravel: 10.0

**React.js**: 10.0

Express.js: 9.0

Ruby on Rail: 8.0

**Html**: 10.0

Css: 9.0

I am a highly experienced professional who specializes in designing, developing, and maintaining mobile applications for various platforms, such as IOS and Android.

I have a deep understanding of programming languages and frameworks, as well as experience with mobile app architecture, and development methodologies.

I typically work with a team of developers, designers, and project managers to ensure the successful delivery of mobile applications that meet business objectives and user needs.

#### **Experience**

# -Alnabali App

Mayaal: Al-Haramayn Int. Apr 2023~ Aug 2023

Techniques used: Flutter, Laravel, Firebase, Google Map,

The purpose of this project is to make reservations to bus companies for employees to go to work at more than 20 factories in Jordan, and the bus companies will accept the reservations and allocate buses and drivers by region. For this purpose, the user has three permissions, geolocation and Geofencing were used to check the area, and FCM was used to notify the result of reservation and assigned tasks.

Here, I worked as an engineer, carried out the overall design of the backend and frontend based on figma, and completed the project by coding alone from beginning to end.

# -PlexyCube

Century 21: Agios Tychonas

Nov 2022 ~ Apr 2023

Techniques used: react-native, QR code scan, Laravel

Google play Url:

#### https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.wirelesspay

This project is a unique Quiz app. In other words, various QR codes are attached to the cube. The app scans the qr code using the camera and displays the appropriate question. A question once asked will not come up again.

This was made according to the idea that several people use dice to randomly present questions and measure the scores accordingly. The app is made with react-native and the backend is made with laravel. An excel file containing more than 30,000 questions is called and data is displayed based on it, and only the location of the excel file is stored in the data base.

JavaScript: 8.0

**Jquery**: 9.0

**Php**: 10.0

BootStrap: 9.0

**Node.js**: 9.0

**MySQL**: 10.0

MongoDB: 10.0

GitHub/Bitbucket: 10.0

### Languages

**English** 

Native

**Spanish** 

Intermediate

This is the core of the backend.

Also, the key to the frontend is that it does a bi-directional search to speed up the search.

# -Trip Jungle

ID SOLUTIONS PERU Valladolid 103, Ate 15012, Peru

Jul 2022 Oct 2022

Techniques used: android-java, AR, Alexa, rest-Api, google-map

This project is an app that helps you to tour the scenic spots of the jungle.

You can see the history and culture of the scenic spot using AR

technology, and there is a voice assistant using alexa.

This project was created using android-java.

In addition, various shortest routes and places are searched using the go ogle map function.

The basic problem here was AR with pokeman-like functionality.

In other words, it was difficult to display AR according to the coordinates through gps, but I did it perfectly.

### -Pronouns

**Al Burj Complex,** Queen Rania St. 91, Jordan Apr 2021 Jun 2022

Techniques used: react-native, rest-Api, Laravel, FTP

Google Play and apple store Url:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mayaal.pronoun

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pronoun/id1530348495

This project is an educational app for kids.

All UIs are automatically created by receiving data from the backend, and by introducing a scoring system, this is a project that helps parents to always know and educate their children about their knowledge level.

The basic problem was that, as it was for children, much was done through drag.

It was made with react-native and includes various fields.

## -WFG Finance

**CodeBright,** 46364 Utica Square, Sterling, VA 20165, United States Jan 2021 Apr 2021

Techniques used: android-java, math, ios-swift, Api

This project was for a real estate company. When renting real estate, various calculations are carried out to calculate profit and loss, and

various changes due to market price after 1 to 10 years, to calculate maintenance cost and write a report.

The default here was math. I knew finance well and had to apply various mathematical formulas to calculate the corresponding values. Made with android-java and ios-swift.

They worked 10 hours a day and conducted many tests to ensure high quality and released them.

### -Netory Invoice

Jobber, Toronto, GA 20165 Canada

Apr 2020 Jan 2021

Techniques used: math, ios-swift, Api(Xml, form-data, json)

This project was to automatically create reports and invoices based on the data entered in various forms and send them to the appropriate email address.

The basic here was to work offline and create invoices in 15 formats. Everything worked out perfectly.

### -SRT conversion

**Skill Bill,** Via della Signora 6 20122 Milano MI Italy Oct 2019 Apr 2020

Techniques used: MacOs, ios-swift

This project is to programmatically import the srt file to adjust the start and end times of the corresponding subtitles and to correct the overall time.

Basically, by importing the srt file, one is to edit the characters by sorting them by start time and the other by end time.

It was built with the corresponding swift for macos.

### -Online Anytime

**WiseTech Global,** 1051 East Woodfied Road Schaumburg IL 60173. 2018 Feb Oct 2019

Techniques used: android-java, ios-swift, firebase, Laravel, volley, alar mofire

This project is to constantly manage the data created using the form and camera when online or offline, and to send a report to the appropriate e mail.

It is also to check the daily workload of the users.

The difficult thing was that the resolution of the image had to be quite high and also avoid amplification compared to the already existing image. Also, it was to eliminate the phenomenon of interruption due to the large capacity and number of images when uploading.

#### Education

### **Kennesaw State University**

**1000 Chastain Rd NW, Kennesaw, GA 30144, USA** 2012-2017 (5 years)

I went to university for 5 years and majored in IT engineering.

I basically learned database management and mobile fields, and also practiced at a large company.

### Qualifications

### **Master of Information Technology**

IT-Park University 88VP+6RQ, Tashkent